<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>the blog of many things.</description>
		<link>/</link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Bling Bling</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Today I got a wonderful surprise in the mail. But first some back story. I did(still do) this cool thing called Drum Corps. For those who haven’t been exposed to it, think marching band on steroids. For the sake of brevity, drum corps and marching band are pretty much the same thing except, drum corps is much cooler, or rather as cool as marching band can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve spent the summers of ‘09 ‘10 ‘11 ‘12 ‘14 devoting my time to the Blue Devils Drum and Bugle Corps. And 4 out of 5 of those summers we went undefeated and won the Drum Corps International World Championship. Yes, there is such a thing and you’ll just have to trust me when I say that it’s much cooler than it sounds. Anyway, when a corps wins, each member is given a championship ring. Think Super Bowl rings but for marching band.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I got my ‘12 ring in the mail. “But wait” you ask, “It’s 2015 and you’re just your 2012 ring?”. Well, drum corps is expensive and the Blue Devils, understandably, don’t give you your ring if you owe them money. Now everything is payed off and I have my ring. All is good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/media/rings.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All the Rings.&quot; /&gt;
From left to right: ‘14 ‘12 ‘10 ‘09&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 10:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
				<link>/drumcorps/2015/02/04/Bling-Bling.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/drumcorps/2015/02/04/Bling-Bling.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The First!</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;So here it is. My new/first Blog! I finally sat down and decided to so something cool with my limited down time (Yes, I’m also watching Netflix at the moment) and create what you’re reading now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to use this blog to openly talk about any and all things that I find worth of placing here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 15:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
				<link>/general/2015/02/03/The-First.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/general/2015/02/03/The-First.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
